what's up guys in this video I'm going to show you how to download a regular
我要去看这个视频中有什么人 向您展示如何下载常规
file from the web and it's a little bit different than just an image file to be
来自网络的文件， 它有点 不只是 一个图像文件 不同的 是
honest it's a little bit more complex but definitely useful so before we get
说实话，它有点复杂 但在我们得到之前肯定是有用的
started I want to show you guys one other thing you know how whenever we
我想开始向你们展示一个 其他的事情你知道我们何时
were importing modules before I just put import and then the name of the module well I'll show you guys on something
在我刚刚放入之前导入模块 进口，然后模块 的名称 好吧，我会 告诉 你们一些事情
else that you might see if you ever see from in something like this
否则你可能会看到，如果你看到 来自这样的事情
oh-ho take it easy that caps-lock import this is a different way that you can
哦，你可以轻松地将大写锁定 导入 这是一种不同的方式， 你可以
import and I'll explain in detail what exactly that means whenever I talk about classes and more about modules later on
导入， 我会详细解释什么 这恰恰 意味着每当我谈论 稍后将有关于模块的类和更多信息
but I just want to get you guys familiar with the syntax right now so you guys aren't confused if you ever see this
但我只是想让你们熟悉 现在使用语法， 所以你们 如果你看到这个，不要混淆
it's just some different way that you can import modules so what I'm going to
这只是你的一些不同方式 可以导入模块，所以我要去
do is I'm going to show you guys how to download a CSV file and you can actually
做的是，我要告诉你们 如何 下载一个CSV文件 ，你 可以
use this same technique whenever you're downloading text file but there aren't
无论何时你都使用同样的技术 下载文本文件，但 目前 还没有
that many text files just flowing around the internet so a CSV file is of course just a comma separated value file just
许多文本文件只是 四处流淌 互联网所以当然是CSV文件 只是一个逗号分隔值文件
like a text file but things are separated with commas so if you go to
就像一个文本文件，但 事情是 用逗号分隔所以如果你去
finance yahoo.com type in the ticker of any company if you
财务yahoo.com 如果您输入任何公司的股票代码
don't know one goog will give you a stock information about Google and whenever you go to a company's um little
不知道一个goog 会给你一个 有关Google和Google的股票信息 每当你去公司的时候都很少
financial page on the left hand side they have hold on a second
在 左侧 的金融 页面 他们坚持一秒钟
got a itch in my hair all right on the left hand side they have historical
在我的 头发 上痒得很好 左手边他们有历史
prices so if you click that it's going to give you just a bunch of their prices
价格如此，如果你点击它就会发生 给你一大堆价格
in history and again you can find any CSV file this is just a one that I remember is free so at the bottom of the
在历史上， 你可以找到 任何 CSV文件这 只是我的一个 记得是免费的，所以在 该 底部
page you're going to see this link that says download the spreadsheet and don't
页面你会看到 这个 链接 说 下载电子表格而不是
click it or else it's going to download the CSV file right to your computer I'm
点击它，否则它将 下载 CSV文件就在你的电脑上 我是
right click it and hit copy link address and if I paste it in there you can see
右键单击它并点击复制链接地址 如果我把它贴在那里你就可以看到
that this is indeed a link to a CSV file so make sure that you have that copies
这确实是CSV文件的链接 所以请确保你有那份 副本
in your clipboard and that's the file that we're going to download again if
在你的剪贴板中，那是文件 我们打算 如果再下载
you know of any other CSV file um feel free to use that but I know that yahoo
你知道任何其他CSV文件 自由使用，但是我知道 ， 雅虎
has a bunch for free so you can use that so of course instead of having to work
有一堆免费，所以你可以使用它 所以当然不必工作
with that long honky-tonkin thing every time
每一次都有 那种长长的 笨蛋 时间
what I want to do is I'm going to save all that in a variable called goog URL
我想要做的就是我要 保存 所有在称为goog URL的变量中
so right now we can just use this variable a lot cleaner if you ask me so
所以现在我们可以只 使用这 如果你这么问我，可变的很多
now that we have a URL of a file that we don't want to download we need to make a
现在我们有 一个文件 的URL 我们 不想下载我们需要做一个
function to of course download crap from that URL so I'm just going to
功能 当然下载 从那个URL废话， 所以我 只是去
name my function download stock data and the parameter we pass it in is your CSV
命名我的功能下载库存数据 和 我们传递的参数是你的 CSV
URL so the URL of some CSV file on the Internet
URL所以 是一些CSV文件 的URL 互联网
alright simple enough so far so now what we need to do is we need to tell our
好吧 很简单， 到目前为止所以现在什么 我们需要做的是我们需要告诉我们的
Python program to connect to the internet first so what we're going to be
Python程序连接到 互联网第一，所以我们将成为
doing is calling a function but it's easier if you store it in a variable
做就是调用一个函数，但它是 如果将它存储在变量中会更容易
called response so this is pretty much think of it as your connection to a
叫响应，所以这几乎是 把它想象成你与a的联系
webpage so we already know how to do this request dot URL see if it's there
网页， 所以我们已经知道该怎么做了 这个请求点URL看看它是否存在
well I guess I might as well tell you bit there it is URL open and what this
好吧，我想我不妨 告诉 你 在那里它是URL打开，这是什么
function does is the only parameter that it takes or that we're going to be
function does是 唯一的参数 它需要或我们将会是
passing in is the URL of a CSV file on the internet again it's the URL of any
传递是 一个CSV 的 URL 文件 上 互联网再次是它的URL
web page but it goes that URL and then it's going to store the connection to
网页， 但它 然后 是那个URL 它将存储连接
that web page in this variable right here response so now that we have that
这个变量中的网页是对的 这里 的响应所以现在我们 有
response we can do something cool with it and I'll show you guys this make another variable call it CSV or whatever
反应，我们可以做一些 很酷的 东西 用 它，我会告诉 你 这些人 另一个变量称为CSV或其他
you want and take that response and call a function on it called read now this is
你想要并接受那个回应 并打电话 它上面的一个函数现在称为read
going to do is it's going to read the data from whatever URL you're pointing
要做的就是阅读 来自您指向的任何URL的数据
to so right now we're reading in all the data which is that huge which
现在我们正在读所有的 那个巨大的数据
pretty much the entire text that's in that file and now we have that text
几乎整个文本 都在 那个文件，现在我们有了那个文本
stored in a variable called CSV so what I want to do now is since we have all
存储在一个名为CSV的变量中 我现在想做的就是因为我们拥有所有
that data stored in a variable called CSV I don't know if that's string data
该数据存储 在一个 名为 的变量中 CSV 我不知道那是否是字符串数据
or maybe it's numerical data maybe it's date data I want to guarantee that that data that we just read in is a
或者它可能是数字数据 也许这是我想要 保证 的日期数据 我们刚刚读到的数据是
string so then we won't have any problems later on so what I can do in
字符串所以我们将不会有任何 以后的问题所以我能做些什么
that case is put CSV underscore STR and remember that function STR right there
那个案例是CSV下划线STR和 记得功能STR就在那里
well this takes anything inside here converts it to a string I think we did
好吧，这里面有任何东西 将它转换为我认为我们做过的字符串
it with numbers whenever we're trying to print out numbers and strings together
每当我们 尝试时，它都带有数字 打印出数字和字符串
so anyways whatever data you read from this file it's going to convert it to a
无论如何你读的数据都是如此 这个文件 将 它 转换 为
string and then it's going to store that in the variable CSV underscore string so
字符串 ，然后它将存储 它 在变量CSV下划线字符串中
now we can use this wherever you would use a string to print it out whatever we
现在我们可以不管你 会 使用这个 使用一个字符串打印出来，无论我们
want to do with it however I'm going to show you guys how to take it and save it to an appropriate file on your computer
我想要用它，但 我要去 告诉 你们如何接受并保存它 到您计算机上的相应文件
so right now we took all that data and it's in one long string like this but
所以现在我们拿走了所有这些数据 这是一个长长的字符串，但是
one big line however if we ever read that in a file of course it's going to
如果我们读过，那就是一条大线 那 当然 是在文件中
be kind of confusing so what we want to do is we want to take it and break it up
有点混乱 所以我们想要的 做的是，我们希望把它和打破它
in lines since if we look to this we don't want all of these numbers and dates on the same line we want each of
在线， 因为如果我们看到这个我们 不想要所有这些 数字 和 在我们 想要的每条 线上的日期
these on a new line whenever we make the file so to do that the first thing you
当我们制作时，这些就在一条新线上 文件，所以你做的第一 件事
need is variable called lines and set it equal to this CSV actually you can just
需要变量称为线并设置它 等于这个CSV实际上你可以
copy this set it equal to your string and call a function called split and in
复制此设置它等于 你的字符串 并调用一个名为 split和in的函数
between quotes put this symbol right here now what split does is it basically
在引号之间放置此符号 现在，分裂的作用 基本上 就是这样
takes a string a huge long string and it breaks it up now how does it know where
带一个字符串一个巨大的长字符串和它 现在打破它怎么 知道在哪里
to break it up just break it up every 10 characters
打破它只是每隔10分解一次 人物
what on sound like someone is on my freaking door which is weird because it is almost 1 a.m. so my doors locked but
什么声音就像有人在我身上 吓人的门，因为它很奇怪 几乎 是 凌晨1点多 ，所以 我的大门紧锁 ，但
anyways it takes a long string and it breaks it up whenever it comes across
无论如何它需要一个长串 而且它 每当碰到它时都会打破它
this new character so instead of having everything on the same line we're going
这个新角色不是没有 我们要去的同一条线上的一切
to go line by line in it's a lot easier to work with it whenever we're making
一行一行就好了 每当 我们制作 时 都要 使用 它
our file so of course what we need to do now is just a stuff we learn before we
我们的文件当然是我们需要做的 现在只是 我们之前学到 的 东西
need to save it somewhere on our computer well we're not going to be like hey we downloaded crap just spin a big
需要把它保存在 我们的 某个地方 计算机以及我们不会 像 嘿，我们下载了废话 只是旋转一个大
roulette wheel on my hard drive and save it somewhere randomly now so let's go
轮盘赌轮在我的硬盘 上并 保存 它现在是随机的， 所以我们走了
ahead and tell our computer where um we actually want to save it so I'll save this to a file named um gube csv now
提前告诉我们的电脑我们在哪里 实际上想保存它 所以我会保存 现在这个名为um gube csv的文件
again remember I think I talked to you guys about this in like the first or
再记得我想 我跟 你 说过 话 关于这个的人就像第一个或第一个
knows must've been like the third tutorial whenever you're working with
知道一定是第三个 无论何时你正在使用教程
file paths it's always good to have our before it that means raw and that means that you can type a file like this like
文件路径它总是好的， 有 我们 在 它 之前 ，这意味着原始的， 这意味着 你可以像这样输入一个文件
something like this see um like oh bulky whatever and you don't have to escape every character so even though I'm just
这样的事情看起来 像是 笨重的哦 什么，你不必逃避 每个角色都是如此，即使我 只是
using the file name with a simple extension I always like to put
使用简单的文件名 扩展我总喜欢 把
everything inside our Raj string just makes good practice I guess so now we
我们 拉吉字符串 内 的一切都只是 做好我的想法我现在就是这样
said where we want to save it now we can use our file objects to read and write
说我们现在可以保存它的地方 使用我们的文件对象进行读写
from it so the first thing we need to do is we need to open up this file so we
从它开始我们需要做的第一件事 是我们需要 打开 这个文件，所以我们
can actually write to it so the first thing it needs it says okay what file do
实际上可以写 第一个 它需要它的东西说 好的文件做什么
you want to open well that one and what do you want to do
你想打开 那一个，你想做什么
to it well since we're taking that data and writing to it or creating it of
因为我们正在接收这些 数据 和写入，或创造 它
course W that's what we learn the last oreal so now that we have a file open
这就是我们最后学到的东西 现在，我们 有一个文件打开
and we can write to it what we want to do is we pretty much want to loop
我们 可以把它写什么 ， 我们要 我们非常想循环
through what we just downloaded and print it on the file so
通过我们刚刚下载的内容 和 将它打印在文件上
the first thing we need is a for loop and what you do is put four line and
我们需要的第一件事是for 循环 而你做的是放四行和
lines and basically what this is going to do is it's going to loop through the
线条，基本上是这样 的 要做的 就是它将循环通过
string and for each individual line I'll show you guys what we're going to do
字符串和每个单独的行 我会 告诉你们我们要做什么
that right now what we're going to do is take the file that we just open and
现在我们要做的是 拿我们 刚打开 的文件
we're going to write to it so remember each line which is each chunk it broke
我们要写信给 所以记住 每条线都是破碎的
up yesterday's line that's what we told it to do right there
这就是我们所说的昨天的路线 它在那里做
so we're going to print the line to the file and then after each one we just
所以我们打算将线打印到 文件， 然后每经过一个刚刚我们
print a new line and that will kick it down to a new line make it real nice and
打印一条新线， 然后踢它 到一个新的线路使它真的很好
beautiful looking so again we said this is what we want to download connect save
美丽的样子，我们再说这个 是我们想要下载 连接保存
it as a string make a file on our computer right to the file the only
它作为一个字符串在我们的文件上 计算机权限到文件 唯一
other thing that we have to do is close this our file object just so we don't
我们要做的其他事情就是关闭 这是我们的文件对象，所以我们 不 这样 做
waste any memory on our computer and then we need to call this function right
浪费我们的计算机上的任何记忆和 然后我们需要正确调用此函数
here so to call it download stock data in the URL they're passing in is of
这里叫它下载股票数据 在 他们 传入 的URL 中
course goog URL so again take note that on the left hand side I deleted all the
当然goog URL所以再次 注意 在左边 我删除了所有
other files that we didn't need from the last tutorials so right now I only have
我们不需要的其他文件 最后的教程，所以我现在只有
main and tuna now whenever I run this I now got this new file goog CSV and if I
主要和金枪鱼现在每当我运行这个我 现在有了这个新文件goog CSV，如果我
double click this to open it oh-ho-ho-ho-ho look at that in formation so now we can take this information and
双击此 将其打开 哦，浩浩浩看着那个 编队 所以现在我们可以把这些信息和
you know pretty much make the perfect algorithm to make us a perfect stock
你知道几乎是完美的 算法让我们成为一个完美的股票
market trader so again if you just you know try to copy all of this and use
市场交易员，如果你 只是你，那么 知道尝试 复制所有这些并使用
your little crappy calculator to try to figure out you know the best time to
你的小蹩脚计算器试图 弄清楚你知道 最好的 时间
sell stocks it's going to be confusing but now in a few lines of code we can
出售股票会让人感到困惑 但现在 我们可以 通过几 行代码
download the historical data for any company in history and we can analyze it
下载任何历史数据 公司在历史上 我们可以 分析 它
and make the perfect program to over the world so we're going to be taken over the world in a couple
并 制作完美的 程序 在世界各地，所以我们将成为 一对夫妇接管世界
tutorials not right away so that's what you have to look forward to but for now
教程不是马上就是这样 你有期待 ，但现在
then guys for watching don't forget subscribe and well smell you guys later
然后观看的人不要 忘记 订阅并 稍后闻到你们的味道